Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2000-074
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/7-9/1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Parent Leadership Institute 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Women's Self-Employment Project 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NCWE Taxes 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Independent Sector 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - HUB taxes 1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Joint Venture Report 8/1992 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N Administrative Memoranda 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Detroit (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - ALF/N Action 1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - ALF/N (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - ALF/N Community Foundations (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - ALF/N Coalition of Community Foundations for Youth 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - ALF/N Trip 6/8-19/1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/2-4/1991 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - ALF/N Ad Hoc Chapter Development, Fundraising Committees (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Corrrespondence, Publications, Notes, etc. (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Enterprise Foundation Hope from Homes packet 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - IRWG packet 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - IRWG 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - IRWG Advisory Council (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - IRWG Women's Health Conference Planning (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Putney School Development (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Putney School 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Putney School General (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Working Assets Common Holdings 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - World Business Academy (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - ALF Miscellaneous 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Independent Sector (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Putney School (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Manchester 7/14-28/1997 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Publications re: Women (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Mayfair Neighborhood Strategic Plan (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Foundation packet 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Foundation Welfare to Work packet (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Business Plan 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 1/1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/21/1998 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee 7/1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Statements 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 7/29/1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation Conference 11/1-4/1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Foundation Publications (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Foundation Correspondence & Memoranda (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Leadership California Speech 8/6/1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Trip 12/19/1996-1/4/1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - International Community Foundation packet 1997 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - CAMEO packet 3/1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Putney School 1996 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - AEO 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - ALF (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes, Publications re: Women (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 4/30/1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Foundation East Palo Alto Brief (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 1/23/1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Foundation Ramsey Visit 8/9-11/1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - YWCA Advisory Committee 1992-1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Spring Foundation (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University Women's Club (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - World Business Academy 1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Leadership California (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Trip 2/27-28/1995 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Publications re: Women (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Guide to California Foundations 1978 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - John Gardner Fellowship Applicant Review 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - ALF/N packet (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - ALF/N Cleveland (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - ALF/N Trip 1995 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ALF/N Board Conference Call 12/7/1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ALF/N Roundtable (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ALF/N Rockefeller Foundation Report (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ALF/N Philadelphia Pew (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Seattle (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N - Enterprise Foundation Trip 5/30-31/1995 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Kansas City (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N Pew Grant Draft (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N Roundtable 1995 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N Kellogg Foundation Proposal 1993 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N Correspondence, Memoranda 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - ALF/Hartford 1992-1995 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - ALF/Houston-Gulf Coast 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - ALF/Houston-Gulf Coast Trip 1/14-15/1993 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - ALF/Mountain Valley – Sacramento 1998 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - ALF/Silicon Valley 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ALF/Oregon 1992-1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - ALF/Tacoma (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - ALF/Tacoma Trip 4/15-16/1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - ALF/N Reckmeyer 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - ALF/N Resource Person RFP 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - ALF/N Resource Person RFP Responses 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ALF/N Research Report-Revised 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - ALF/N Research Report Summary (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N Research Report Revisions (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N Resources - Coalition of Community Foundations for Youth (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N Resources – Equity Institute (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N Resources – Collaborative Leadership Materials (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N Research 1991 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N Research Reports 1991-1995 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N Research - Burns (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - ALF/N Press (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development General (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Report Draft 1992 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Leadership California (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Hero 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Los Angeles (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Maine Consensus Project 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Mountain Valley/Sacramento (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Newark (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development New Hampshire (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development New York (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Oakland 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development San Francisco (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development San Diego (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development San Mateo (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Santa Fe (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Syracuse (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - ALF/N Board Development Committee (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - ALF/N Board Galitz (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - ALF/N Board Jaworski (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - ALF/N Board Memoranda (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - ALF/N Board Information (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - ALF/N Lenoe McCracken (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - ALF/N Patrick (Consultant) (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - ALF/N Shanks Chapter Development (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - ALF/N Sloss (Executive Director) (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - ALF/N Wage & Benefit Survey (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - ALF/N Consultants (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Meeting 2/17/1995 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Meeting 2/24/1994 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Conference Call 8/23/1993 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Conference Call 8/27/1992 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Meeting 10/7/1991 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 4/28-30/1994 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - ALF/N River Oaks Loans (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - ALF/N Financial Oversight, Audit Committee Meetings (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - ALF/N Bookkeeping (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - ALF/N Finances 1992 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - ALF/N Reimbursements (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 3/2/1996 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 4/27-29/1995 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - ALF/N Board/Executive Committee (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Stanford Associates Speech 2/2/1988 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - HUB 10/1988 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Study Circles packet (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Academy of Leadership 6/5/1998 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda, Publications 1996-1999 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 7/22-8/21997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Measure O Speech 10/141/1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Academy of Leadership Report 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - AEO Trip 5/5-8/1999 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Putney School Heller Foundation 1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Putney School Hewlitt (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Putney School Development (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Aid to Artisans packet (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda 1989-1998 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Richard Lyman Correspondence (some personal) 1981-1989 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Aglae "Ba" Lyman Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Aglae "Ba" Lyman Memorial (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Bag of Conference Badges & Nametags (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Personal Cards & Correspondence 1980-1999 - RESTRICTED (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Personal Cards & Correspondence 1993-1999 – RESTRICTED (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Framed certificates (Box 43 os)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2001-229
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2014-100
  - Current Curriculum Vitae (ESL), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Edith Gelles 70th birthday piece for IRWG Newsletter, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1984-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CHRON - ESL, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - OH Current Events Talk, 2004 Jan 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gardner Fellows, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - RWL/ESL Exemplary Leader - ALF, 2003 Oct 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Press Coverage, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Press Inquiries, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the Editor, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Gardner Fellows, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AEO (Association for Enterprise Opportunity) Policy Com, 2002-2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AEO, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - California Association for Microenterprise Opportunity (CAMEO), 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ALF (American Leadership Forum)/N, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Current Events Report, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Current Events Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Current Events, 2007 Jan 8 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Current Events: ESL Talk and Summary and Preamble for "Scribble and Stretch", 2006 April (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Current Events Members, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Current Events, 2003 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Current Events, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Current Events, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Current Events, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Enterprise Foundation - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A Guide for Greening Affordable Housing, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Enterprise Foundation - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2004 Jun 16 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Foundation Center - Trustees Emeritus, 1997-2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Current World Affairs, 1998-2007 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Clayman Institute for Gender Research, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Clayman Institute Advisory Board Papers, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Clayman Institute Advisory Board Meeting, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Enrollment and Degrees Data, 1996-2006 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clayman Institute Board Meeting, 2007 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Clayman Institute, 2006 Nov 5-6 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - NAP for Clayman Institute, 2006 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - NAP for Clayman Institute, 2005 Nov 5 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - NAP for Clayman Institute, 2008 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Clayman Institute for Gender Research Papers (1/4), 2002-2008 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Clayman Institute for Gender Research Papers (2/4), 2002-2008 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Clayman Institute for Gender Research Papers (3/4), 2002-2008 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Clayman Institute for Gender Research Papers (4/4), 2002-2008 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Institute for Research on Woman and Gender National Advisory Panel, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Research on Woman and Gender National Advisory Panel Meeting Minutes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - IRWG - Pres. Council Nat. Panel, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Inst. for Research on Women and Gender IRWG, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - IRWG: Suzanne Estler, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Midpeninsula Citizens for Fair Housing, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - PA Endowment Fund - Advisor, 1999-2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Putney 98-99, 1998-2007 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University Women's Club, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - WAGES 9/29/05 Event, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 4/7/00 WAGES - Afternoon Gathering, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - WAGES Women's Action to Gain Economic Security, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - W + P: Trustee Connection, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - World Business Academy, 1998-2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - IRWG- ESL 70th/ Gelles, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Aid to Artisans, 1990-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ATA News, 1986-1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - African Leadership Forum, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ALF/SV, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Alumnae Resources, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ashoka, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Aspen Institute, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Association of Jr. Leagues, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Association for Women in Dev. AWID, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Avenidas, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Beijing Action and Resource Network, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Career Action Center, 1989-1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Catalyst, 1989-2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - CDFI, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Center for Employment and Training, SJ, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Stanford Child and Family Services, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Children Now, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Citizen's Trust, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Community Foundation of Silicon Valley, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Corp for Enterpreise Dev, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cooperative Home Care Associates, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Council on Economics Priorities 1991, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Council on Foundations, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Emily's List, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - EPA Can Do, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Equal Rights Advocates, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Families in Transition, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fannie Mae, 1990-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Free at Last, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Greenleaf Center, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Habitat for Humanity (Peninsula), 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hidden Villa, 1995-2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - US Dept of Housing and Urban Development, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Giving Voice to Your Heart, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Independent Sector, 1995-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - International Museum of Women, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - IWRAW International Women's Rights Action Watch, 1992-2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Joint Venture/Silicon Valley, 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Leaders for Community Development [LCD], 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Leadership Palo Alto, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - MentorNet, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Medical Education for South African Blacks, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - IDAs, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - National Foundation for Women Business Owners, 1990-2005 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NAWBO Surveys, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - National Civic League, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1992-1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - National Council for Research on Women (empty), undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - National Neighborhood Coalition, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Office of Refugee Resettlement, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Professional and Business Women's Conference, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Pegasus, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Peninsula Community Foundation, 1997-2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Positive Coaching Alliance, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Responsible Wealth, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Results, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Next Generation Leadership, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Rosenberg Foundation, 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - The Sister Fund, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Springboard Forward, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Social Security, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Entrepreneurship Action Day, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Stanford Business School, 1990-2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 07 JWG Fellows, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 2006 Gardner Fellows (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 2003 Gardner Fellows (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 2001 Gardner Fellows Selection (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Haas Public Service Center, 2001-2007 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - SU Women's Club, 1991-2004 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Swarthmore "The Woman with the Flying Hair", 1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Time Management Inc, 1987-1999 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Trickle Up Program, 1989-2007 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - TWF: The Women's Foundation of San Francisco, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - UNIFEM, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Venture Philanthropy, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Victorian Women's Trust, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Wingspread, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Women's Funding Network, 1997, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Women's Funding Network (Old), 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - WAF/CP: Bancel, Diane, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Women and Philanthropy II, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - WAF/CP, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Global Women's Leadership Center, 2005 Mar 30 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N - Carolyn Barnes, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N Admin - Sherifa O. Edoga, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N Admin - Evangeline Koch, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Evangeline Koch, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - EHK - Leadership for A changing World Application, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters and Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - ALF - Houston, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - ALF / Mt. Valley - California, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - ALF- Silicon Valley, 2000-2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Trip Academy of Leadership Folder, 2000 May 22-24 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Academy of Leadership, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Leadership America, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Enterprise Community Partners, Inc., 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 Sept 13 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 Dec 13 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Meeting of the Financial Review Committee, 2007 Mar 13 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 Mar 13 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 Mar 14 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 Jun 13 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2004 Jan 14 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Board of Trustees Meeting, 2003 Dec 10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines, 2003 Sept 09 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NP Enterprise, 2003 Sept 9-10 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Women's Network, 1999 Aug 9 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2003 Sept 10 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Enterprise Foundation, 2003 Sept 4 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Enterprise Foundation, 2000 Apr 25 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Trip Enterprise Board Meeting Washington DC, 2000 Nov 9 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation, 2000 Nov 9 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting Board of Trustees, 2000 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - The Enterprise Foundation Atlanta, 2000 May 4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2001 Feb 7 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Agenda Executive Committee and Financial Review and Audit Committee, 2001 Feb 6 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - The Hub Co-Ventures for Women's Enterprise, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - TWA 013837611, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 00 Contribs Pending, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - The Women's Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Women and Philanthropy Annual Meeting Conference Committee, 2003 Feb 19 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - The Enterprise Foundation Memorandum, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - The Enterprise Foundation Memorandum, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Article "Casualties at Home", 2003 Mar 27 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Phone number for Nicole Gudzowsky, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Building communities of opportunity, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Failing to make ends meet: A report on the economic status of women in California, 2002 May (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fax memo: Invitation to Jane Fonda, 2003 Jan 2 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Fax on potential donors, 2003 Jan 7 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Fax: Accepted invitation to be keynote speakers, 2003 Jan 8 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Fax: Assistant Director announcement, 2003 Jan 8 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Invitations to speak at annual meeting, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - WAP Annual Meeting Committee List, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - WAP Member Letter, 2002 Sep (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Educator, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Invitation to CSI luncheon, 2002 May 22 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Women's Philanthropy Institute, 2002 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Book proposal from Mary Ellen Capek, 2002 May 20 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Women and Philanthropy The First 25 Years, 2002 Apr 3 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Email exchange with Meghan McCleary, 2002 Aug 11 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Personal correspondence, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Twenty Vital Years 2001 Annual Report (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - FIELD funder guide, 2006 Jan-Feb (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - The Role of Microenterprise Development in the United States, 2001 Mar (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - FIELD funder guide, 2007 Apr (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - MicroTest, 2005 Sep (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Association for Enterprise Opportunity, 2002 Jul (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - AEO Nomination Support, 2002 Jul (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - AEO Exchange, 2001 Apr-Jun (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Women's Initiative Mailer, 2000 Jan 02 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - BusinessWoman, 2000 Dec (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - National Foundation for Woman Business Owners, 2000 Nov (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - WUSTL, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development Annual Report, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Center for Social Development, 2001 Feb (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Aspen: Self/Field, 1999 Aug (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - AEO mailings and materials, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Channing Long Range, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Channing Future, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Mosquito Abatement District, 2005 Nov (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - AEO Exchange, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Women & Philanthropy letter, List of Members of the Executive Committee and Board, 2001 Feb. 15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - New York Times Giving Section, 2000 Nov. 20 (Box 6, Folder 2)